Guide to the Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York Records WAG.009
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Addendum, 1957-2004; 107103
  - Subseries F: General Files, 1957-2004; 107104
    - Staten Island Community College: Newsletter, 1973-1975; 107192 (Box 187, Folder 11)
    - State University of New York (SUNY), 1970-1973; 107191 (Box 187, Folder 12)
    - SUNY, 1981; 107190 (Box 187, Folder 13)
    - SUNY, 1985-1986; 107189 (Box 187, Folder 14)
    - SUNY, 1987-1992; 107188 (Box 187, Folder 15)
    - SUNY, 1993-1997; 107187 (Box 187, Folder 16)
    - SUNY: Clippings, 1976-1986; 107186 (Box 187, Folder 17)
    - SUNY: Constitution and Bylaws, 1972; 107185 (Box 187, Folder 18)
    - Strikes, 1975-1990; 107184 (Box 187, Folder 19)
    - Student Demonstrations, 1991-1999; 107183 (Box 187, Folder 20)
    - Student Evaluation of Faculty, 1972-1974; 107182 (Box 187, Folder 21)
    - Student Life Personnel Committee, 1974-1975; 107181 (Box 187, Folder 22)
    - Students, 1972-1996; 107180 (Box 187, Folder 23)
    - Student Voter Registration, 1976; 107179 (Box 187, Folder 24)
    - Summer Hours, 1975-1978; 107178 (Box 187, Folder 25)
    - Tarrytown Conference, 1975-1979; 107177 (Box 187, Folder 26)
    - Task Force on Higher Education, 1975-1978; 107176 (Box 187, Folder 27)
    - Taylor, Harold, 1982; 107175 (Box 187, Folder 28)
    - Tax Deferred Annuity, 1974-1998; 107174 (Box 187, Folder 29)
    - Teacher Education, 1972-1973; 107173 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Teacher Education, 1977; 107172 (Box 188, Folder 2)
    - Teacher Education, 1986-1988; 107171 (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - Teacher Insurance and Annuity Association, 1996-1999; 107170 (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - Teacher Recruitment: Internship Project, 1986; 107169 (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - Teacher Recruitment: Internship Project, 1987; 107168 (Box 188, Folder 6)
    - Teacher Retirement System, 1973-1995; 107167 (Box 188, Folder 7)
    - Telecourses, 1982; 107166 (Box 188, Folder 8)
    - Temporary Commission on the Future of Post Secondary Education, 1977; 107165 (Box 188, Folder 9)
    - Tenure, 1973-1976; 107164 (Box 188, Folder 10)
    - Tilden Financial Corporation: Insurance, 1969; 107163 (Box 188, Folder 11)
    - Transit Strike, 1980-1999; 107162 (Box 188, Folder 12)
    - Trent, Richard, 1978; 107161 (Box 188, Folder 13)
    - Tuition, 1972-1979; 107160 (Box 188, Folder 14)
    - Tuition Assistance Program (TAP), 1981; 107159 (Box 188, Folder 15)
    - Tuition Tax Credit Bills, 1978-1981; 107158 (Box 188, Folder 16)
    - Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board, 1975-1976; 107157 (Box 188, Folder 17)
    - United Federation of Teachers (UFT), undated; 107156 (Box 188, Folder 18)
    - UFT: Correspondence, 1973-1989; 107155 (Box 188, Folder 19)
    - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare: Office of Civil Rights, 1975; 107154 (Box 188, Folder 20)
    - United States Department of Labor, 1974; 107153 (Box 188, Folder 21)
    - United States Department of State, 1978; 107152 (Box 188, Folder 22)
    - United University Professions (UUP), 1975-1992; 107151 (Box 188, Folder 23)
    - UUP, 1994-1999; 107150 (Box 188, Folder 24)
    - University Faculty Senate, 1971-1979; 107149 (Box 188, Folder 25)
    - University Faculty Senate, 1980-1983; 107148 (Box 188, Folder 26)
    - University Faculty Senate, 1984-1985; 107147 (Box 188, Folder 27)
    - University Faculty Senate, 1986-1988; 107146 (Box 188, Folder 28)
    - University Faculty Senate, 1990-1994; 107145 (Box 188, Folder 29)
    - University Faculty Senate, 1995; 107144 (Box 188, Folder 30)
    - University Faculty Senate, 1996-1997; 107143 (Box 188, Folder 31)
    - University Faculty Senate, 1998-2000; 107142 (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - University Student Senate, 1971-1985; 107141 (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - Urban Higher Education Research Forum, 1982; 107140 (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - Vladeck, Judith, 1993-1994; 107139 (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - University Faculty Senateladeck, Stephen, 1972-1980; 107138 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Voorhees Technical Institute, 1973-1985; 107137 (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - Washington Federation of Teachers, 1998; 107136 (Box 189, Folder 7)
    - Water Conservation Committee, 1986-1988; 107135 (Box 189, Folder 8)
    - Website, 1997; 107134 (Box 189, Folder 9)
    - Weinberg, Beryl, 1976-1981; 107133 (Box 189, Folder 10)
    - Welfare Fund, 1972-1979; 107132 (Box 189, Folder 11)
    - Welfare Fund, 1980-1983; 107131 (Box 189, Folder 12)
    - Welfare Fund, 1984-1985; 107130 (Box 189, Folder 13)
    - Welfare Fund, 1986-1987; 107129 (Box 189, Folder 14)
    - Welfare Fund, 1988-1989; 107128 (Box 189, Folder 15)
    - Welfare Fund, 1990-1993; 107127 (Box 189, Folder 16)
    - Welfare Fund, 1990-1999; 107126 (Box 189, Folder 17)
    - Welfare Fund Newsletter, 1990-1993; 107125 (Box 189, Folder 18)
    - Welfare: Trustees Benefits, 1982; 107124 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Wilson, Harold (PSC Vice President), 1975-1977; 107123 (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - Wilson, Harold (PSC Vice President), 1978-1979; 107122 (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Wilson, Harold (PSC Vice President), 1980-1981; 107121 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Wilson, Harold (PSC Vice President), 1982-1989; 107120 (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - Winter, Joseph, 1982; 107119 (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - Women's Studies, 1982; 107118 (Box 190, Folder 7)
    - Workload, 1971-1981; 107117 (Box 190, Folder 8)
    - Workload, 1982-1983; 107116 (Box 190, Folder 9)
    - Workmen's Circle, 1975; 107115 (Box 190, Folder 10)
    - Yellowitz, Irwin, 1984-1989; 107114 (Box 190, Folder 11)
    - York College Chapter, 1972-1984; 107113 (Box 190, Folder 12)
    - York College Chapter, 1985-1992; 107112 (Box 190, Folder 13)
    - York College Chapter, 1993-1994; 107111 (Box 190, Folder 14)
    - York College Chapter, 1995; 107110 (Box 190, Folder 15)
    - York College Chapter, 1996-2000; 107109 (Box 190, Folder 16)
    - York College Chapter: Grievances, 1980; 107108 (Box 190, Folder 17)
    - York College Chapter: Newsletter, 1974-1980; 107107 (Box 190, Folder 18)
    - Zeller, Belle, 1975-1991; 107106 (Box 190, Folder 19)
    - Zuccotti, John: New York City Deputy Mayor, 1976; 107105 (Box 190, Folder 20)
- Series VII: Photographs and Audiovisual Materials, 1960s-1999; 464732
  Series VII: Photographs and Audiovisual Materials, contains photographs, negatives, and contact sheets related to faculty and PSC chapters at various campuses, as well as CUNY programs and administration, PSC affiliate groups, PSC officers, and PSC meetings and events. This series also includes some audiovisual materials.
  Arrangement
  Most of this series maintains the original arrangement of the photographs by Aaron Alexander, former Associate Executive Director of PSC.
  - Photographs, Contact Sheets, and Negatives re: Administration (CUNY), Admission Services (CUNY), Affiliate: AUP (American Association of University Professors, Affiliate: AFT (American Federation of Teachers), Affiliate: NYSUT (New York State United Teachers), Affiliate: UFT (United Federation of Teachers), Affiliate: United University Professions (SUNY), Alumni (CUNY), Arbitrators AAA, B.A. Program, Baruch College Faculty, Baruch NCSCBHEP, Baruch PSC Chapter, Board of Trustees- Board of Higher Education (CUNY), Bronx Community Faculty, and Bronx PSC Chapter, 1970s-1980s; 464733 (Box 222)
  - Photographs, Contact Sheets, and Negatives re: Brooklyn College Faculty, Brooklyn College PSC Chapter, Brooklyn Educational Opportunity Center PSC Chapter, Career Counseling and Placement Assoc. (CUNY), Central Office Chapter, Chancellors Reception for Scholars/Distinguished Professors (CUNY), City College Faculty, City College NY-PSC Chapter, Computer Center (CUNY), Committee for Public Higher Education, Conferences- PSC, Delegate Assembly- PSC, Educational Opportunity Center (CUNY), Emergency Financial Control Board (CUNY), Faculty Development, Florida Chapter- PSC, General Equivalency Diploma (CUNY), Graduate School Faculty, and Graduate School PSC Chapter, 1970s-1980s; 464734 (Box 223)
  - Photographs, Contact Sheets, and Negatives re: Graphics/ Cartoons, Higher Education Officers- PSC Chapter, History- PSC Chapter (1972-1980), History/Events- PSC, Hostos Community College, Hostos PSC Chapter, Hunter Campus Schools Chapter, and Hunter College Faculty, 1970s-1980s; 464735 (Box 224)
  - Photographs, Contact Sheets, and Negatives re: Hunter PSC Chapter, Illustrative Photos (Students/Profs in Action), Instructional Resource Center (CUNY), John Jay College Faculty, John Jay PSC Chapter, Kingsborough Community Faculty, Kingsborough PSC Chapter, LaGuardia Community Faculty, LaGuardia PSC Chapter, Legislative Conference, Legislators/ Public Figures, Lehman College Faculty, and Lehman College PSC Chapter, 1970s-1980s; 464736 (Box 225)
  - Photographs, Contact Sheets, and Negatives re: Library Association- PSC (LACUNY), Lobbying- PSC, Manhattan Community Faculty, Manhattan Community PSC Chapter, Manhattan Education Opportunity Center PSC Chapter, Medgar Evers Faculty, Medgar Evers PSC Chapter, Meetings- PSC, Miscellaneous- PSC, Miscellaneous Shots- Early Officers, Mystery Contacts and Negs., National Education Association, Negatives (1975), New York City, New York State, Personnel- PSC, Personnel- PSC (Adjunct Professors), and Personnel- PSC (Executive Council), 1970s-1980s; 464768 (Box 226)
  - Photographs, Contact Sheets, and Negatives re: Personnel- PSC (Former Officers and Staff), Personnel- PSC (Grievance Counselors), Personnel- PSC (IHP), Personnel- PSC (Professional Staff), Personnel- PSC (Support Staff), Personnel- PSC (Welfare Fund), Private Colleges and Universities, Promotional Photographs, Public Figures, Queens College Chapter, Queens College Faculty, and Queensborough CC Faculty, 1970s-1980s; 464769 (Box 227)
  - Photographs, Contact Sheets, and Negatives re: Queensborough CC PSC Chapter, Registrars PSC Chapter, Research Foundation PSC Chapter, Retirees PSC Chapter, Retirees PSC Chapter - Ed Daily, Staten Island College Faculty, Staten Island PSC Chapter, Technical College Faculty- NYC, Technical College PSC Chapter, University Student Center (CUNY), York College Faculty, York College PSC Chapter, Vorhees Tech. Inst. PSC Chapter, Retirees, Irwin Polishook, "Why Go to College?", United Federation of College Teachers, Beller Zeller Scholarship Fund, Arthur Kraus, and Unlabeled, 1960s-1980s; 464770 (Box 228)
  - Six Cassette Tapes (three labeled "3 Radio Spots," two labeled "Neighborhood," and one labeled ":60 Radio 1) Neighborhood 2) Faculty") and Twenty-Three VHS Tapes ("Assembly Updates," "CUNY in Concert," "Jack Bigel with Victor Bigel," "Diversity In Education and NYSUT," "Jack Bigel with Walter Wriston," "Metroview: with Interim Chancellor," "NCSCBEP Conference -- Restoring Authority: Strong Presidents, Faculty Unions and Trustees," "NY 1 with Interim Chancellor," "Oral History- Jack Bigel and Barry Feinstein," "Oral History- Jack Bigel and Lewis Rudin," "PSCTV," "Science and the Written Word by Ronald Hoffman," "Voter Registration PSA," and "CUNY Voter Registration/Drop Out Rate"), 1992-1999; 464771 (Box 229)
  - Photographs of Belle Zeller, 1972; 464784 (Box OS001)
  - Belle Zeller award, 1988 (Box Shared Tamiment 018, Folder 20)
  - Seven VHS tapes, Two Betacam (Women's Conference), 1997-2000 (Box 236)